(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
WONDER SHOWER MUSICAL
Akirose 4th Birthday Live
本日は、アキロゼ生誕祭2022にご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending Akirose Birthday Festival 2022 today.
公演のスクショ、GIF等の一部を切り抜く動画は大歓迎です。
Screenshots of the performance, GIFs, and video clips of parts of it are very welcome.
ハッシュタグは、#アキロゼ生誕祭2022 をつけてたくさん投稿してくださいね。
Please post a lot with the hashtag #AkiroseBirthdayFestival2022.
歌をまるっと投稿するのはご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from posting the entire song.
4度目の生誕祭は、今までと一味違うテイストでお届けいたします。
This 4th birthday festival will be delivered with a slightly different taste than before.
ですが、公演前にとりあえずチャンネル登録お願いいたします。
But first, please subscribe to the channel before the performance starts.
お済みでない方は、今ならなんと無料でチャンネル登録ができます。
For those who haven't yet, you can subscribe for free right now.
というのは冗談ではありません。
And that is not a joke.
はい、窓をのぞいていきますよ。せーの。
Alright, I'm going to peek through the window. One, two...
はい、よくできました。
Yes, well done.
本日は、愉快なホロライブの仲間たちと繰り広げる、不思議な世界をお楽しみください。
Please enjoy the mysterious world we'll create today with my fun Hololive friends.
それでは、アキロゼ 4thバースデーライブ『Wonder Shower Musical』開演いたします。
And now, Akirose 4th Birthday Live "Wonder Shower Musical" begins.
最後まで楽しんでってね！
Please enjoy it until the end!
お話をしよう　昔話より
Let's tell a story, better than an old tale
Alice in Musicland
作詞・作曲：OSTER project
Lyrics & Music: OSTER project
もっともっと素敵な　おとぎ話
A much, much more wonderful fairy tale
ふと目を開けると　真っ白なウサギ
When I suddenly opened my eyes, a pure white rabbit...
大慌てで駆けてく
...was running away in a great hurry.
後を追うの
I'll follow it.
チクタクチクタク急がないと間に合わないわな
Tick-tock, tick-tock, if I don't hurry, I won't make it!
あぁ、チクタクチクタク遅刻するのはもう嫌だ
Ah, tick-tock, tick-tock, I'm tired of being late.
そらチクタクチクタク時間はどんどん減っていく
Look, tick-tock, tick-tock, time is running out.
もうとにかく僕には時間がない
Anyway, I have no time!
ねぇ、そんなに慌てて一体全体どうしたの？
Hey, why are you in such a hurry? What on earth happened?
どこかの誰かといつだかどこかで
Someone, somewhere, sometime...
さあ、壁時計チクタクとっても
Come on, the wall clock's ticking,
時間にシビアだよ
it's really strict with time.
そんなに？
Is it that bad?
そうさ
That's right.
だって彼女は女王様！
Because she's the Queen!
かくかくしかじかチクタクどうにも時間がないから
This and that, tick-tock, there's just no time at all!
ハシゴがあるなら窓の期待にしておくれ
If there's a ladder, put it against the window for me.
それなら一つだけ教えて なぜそんな時でも
In that case, tell me just one thing: Why, even at a time like this,
陽気に歌を歌うの？
do you sing so cheerfully?
それは
That's because it's...
Music Land!
Wonder Land!
ここがMusic Landだからさ！
Because this is Music Land!
じゃ、お先に失礼。またお暇までバイバイさよなら！
Well then, excuse me. Until we're free again, bye-bye, farewell!
待って！
Wait!
あぁ なんて不思議な世界なのでしょう
Ah, what a mysterious world this is.
この先は何が待ってるかしら
I wonder what's waiting ahead.
お嬢さん。
Young lady.
え？
Huh?
お嬢さん。
Young lady.
私？
Me?
そう、お嬢さん。
Yes, young lady.
なに？
What?
君は誰？
Who are you?
私の名前は…
My name is...
君は名前なの？
Are you just a name?
そういうあなたは誰なの？
Then, who are you?
Who am I? 問いかけてみよう
Who am I? Let's try asking.
なぜ？
Why?
Who am I? 分からないんだ
Who am I? I don't know.
Who are you? ねぇ、教えてよ
Who are you? Come on, tell me.
Who am I? 曖昧さ
Who am I? It's ambiguous.
ただ分かってるのは 歌ってる僕は最高にハッピーってこと
All I know is that when I'm singing, I'm at my happiest.
You love music 歌声 歌えば
You love music, if you let your voice sing out...
少しずつ見えてくる
...little by little, you'll start to see it.
僕が生きる意味はきっとここにある
The meaning of my existence is surely right here.
だってそう僕は
Because that's right, I am...
そうきっと私も
Yes, surely I am too...
最高のシンガーなのさ！
The greatest singer!
この風変わりなリズムはどこからやってくるのかしら
I wonder where this peculiar rhythm is coming from.
そりゃ私だよ 帽子屋ことマッドハッターさ
Well, that's me! The hatter known as the Mad Hatter!
腰掛けたら始めるぞ
Sit down and let's get started!
お茶はいかが？
How about some tea?
楽しく飲めば世界も踊る
If you drink it happily, the world will dance too.
お茶はいかが？
How about some tea?
さあ、お茶をどうぞ！
Come, have some tea!
なんて変なフレイバー！
What a strange flavor!
牡丹の味に慣れちまったら
Once you get used to the taste of peonies,
全てが退屈になっちまうものさ
everything else becomes boring.
ありきたりのものじゃつまらない
Ordinary things are just boring.
それも知った奴はみんなイカレちまうのさ
Everyone who knows that ends up going mad!
ほら、お茶はいかが？
Look, how about some tea?
お茶はいかが？
How about some tea?
気をてらいだけじゃイカレちまえ
You'll go mad if you just try too hard!
お茶はいかが？
How about some tea?
さあ、お茶をどうぞ！
Come, have some tea!
そう、イカレりゃ楽しいティータイム！
Yes, when you're mad, it's a fun tea time!
レディメイド
Lady Made
作詞・作曲：すりぃ
Lyrics/Composition: Surii
Lonely, lonely 夜はない侘しさに
Lonely, lonely, in the loneliness where night doesn't end,
頬杖ついてる
resting my chin on my hands.
...とか変わらないわかってるんだよ I'm baby
...I know it doesn't change, I'm baby
ありふれたモブなんだって
Just a common mob
認めてないならいっそ猿真似叫んで
If you won't admit it, just shout like a mimic monkey
威風堂々せいぜい空回りに
Majestic at best, just spinning in circles
本音ばかりじゃ生きられない
Can't live on true feelings alone
録画ビデオで凝る人生が
A life spent fussing over recorded videos
きっとお似合いだわ
Surely suits you well
もっと波なれば溶け込んで
If you become more like waves, you'll blend in
金と愛情で踊るのさ
Dancing for money and affection
ワン・ツー・スリーで弾け飛んだ
Bursting on 1, 2, 3
固定概念をバトる打って 到底 到底
Battling fixed concepts, impossible, impossible
楽ならもう一回
If it's easy, do it once more
レディメイドの琴線に
On the heartstrings of the ready-made
歪みかけてノイズ交じり 後悔 後悔
Starting to distort, mixed with noise, regret, regret
やめて黙ってよ
Stop it, be quiet
下に乗った苦い感情 暴露ばかり吐き出して
Venting out all the bitter emotions that were suppressed
ダーティー ダーティー 言葉飲み込めばほら
Dirty, dirty, if you swallow your words, look
お利口回るようなんて 顔色伺ってるんだよ
Like an obedient child, just watching the mood
I'm baby 歪みだすバブなんだって
I'm baby, just a distorting infant
オーダーメイドのブランド 身に着けて威張って
Boasting in order-made brands
舌を鳴らせば下世話に問う 不適合者は間違いさ
If you click your tongue, the vulgar ones ask, being a misfit is a mistake
かたかたかたかたひろぶって きっと楽なんだな
Clinging to a rigid shell, it must be easy
社会居場所はどこですか
Where is the place in society?
金も愛情もくそ食らえ
To hell with money and affection
ワン・ツー・スリーでくたばり飛んだ
Dropped dead on 1, 2, 3
固定概念を真っ黒塗って どうだい どうだい
Painting fixed concepts pitch black, how's that, how's that?
待っててもらっていろ
Just wait for me
レディメイドの艶美に
In the beauty of the ready-made
解凍を掛けてノイズはじけ
Unfreezing and bursting with noise
問題 問題 解かず歌ってよ
Problem, problem, sing without solving it
塞ぎこんだ黒い感情 暴露ばかり吐き出して
Venting out all the dark emotions that were pent up
ねぇほらまた始まった
Hey, look, it's started again
比較ばかりで飽きたんだ
I'm tired of all the comparisons
大人になどはなりたくなんかないか
I don't want to become an adult or anything
天邪鬼なら放っといて
If you're perverse, just leave me alone
私 私 気付いたの
I, I realized it
ワン・ツー・スリーで弾け飛んだ
Bursting on 1, 2, 3
固定概念をバトる打って 到底 到底
Battling fixed concepts, impossible, impossible
楽ならもう一回
If it's easy, do it once more
レディメイドの琴線に
On the heartstrings of the ready-made
歪みかけてノイズ交じり 後悔 後悔
Starting to distort, mixed with noise, regret, regret
やめて黙ってよ
Stop it, be quiet
ワン・ツー・スリーでくたばり飛んだ
Dropped dead on 1, 2, 3
固定概念を真っ黒塗って どうだい どうだい
Painting fixed concepts pitch black, how's that, how's that?
本当だえいと
It's true
レディメイドの艶美に
In the beauty of the ready-made
解凍を掛けてノイズはじけ
Unfreezing and bursting with noise
問題 問題 解かず歌ってよ
Problem, problem, sing without solving it
下に乗った苦い感情 暴露ばかり吐き出して
Venting out all the bitter emotions that were suppressed
迷い込んだ森の中 私をいざなう声が
In the forest I strayed into, a voice beckons me
深い霧にこだまする 私の道はどっち
Echoing through the thick mist, which way is my path?
あっち そっち それともこっち? 有情不断な お嬢さん
Over there, that way, or this way? Oh, indecisive young lady
だけどそれは私も同じ あっちもそっちも 歩く道
But it's the same for me, a path to walk both there and that way
さあ 喜びや 悲しみや 愛しさまで
Come, from joy, to sorrow, and even to love
形にしたいもの全部 塗り重ねていったら
If I keep layering everything I want to give form to
最初にもとめていたものが 何かわからなくなって
I'll lose sight of what I was looking for at first
最後に残されたものは
And what is left at the end
透明な感情の音楽
Is the music of transparent emotions
個性の残骸
The wreckage of individuality
ずっと追えるのか
Will I keep chasing forever?
誰も分からない
No one knows
頭の中はごちゃごちゃでも
Even if my head is a mess
透明なのも悪くない
Being transparent isn't bad either
だけど決めた 私は決めた
But I've decided, I've decided
私の道
My path
アイショボ！アイショボ！アイショボ！...
Aishobo! Aishobo! Aishobo!...
あれ、ロボ子さんにルーナちん！
Oh, Roboco-san and Luna-chin!
アイショボ、アキちゃん！
Aishobo, Aki-chan!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
おめでとうなのら〜！
Congratulations nanora~!
ありがとう〜！うわ〜！
Thank you~! Whoa~!
お祝いしに来てくれたの？
Did you come to celebrate?
今日はお誕生日ということで クイズを持ってきたのらよ
Since it's your birthday, we've brought a quiz nanora
そうだよ 僕たちが考えた構成のクイズだよ
Yeah, it's a quiz that we came up with
え、お誕生日にクイズ？全然分かんないんだけど
Eh, a quiz for my birthday? I don't get it at all
え？分からないのら？
Eh? You don't understand?
まあ お誕生日といえばクイズでしょ
Well, a quiz is a must for a birthday
いやいや 全然初めて聞いたよ そんなの
No, no, I've never heard of that before
ま とりあえず専用ステージにジャンプなのら！
Well, anyway, let's jump to the special stage nanora!
そうなのら 行くのらよ なになになに
That's right. Let's go nanora. What, what, what?
さ 手つないで
Now, hold hands
行くぞ ジャンプ！
Here we go, jump!
せーの ジャンプ！
One, two, jump!
あー着いたー！
Ah, we're here!
待って ここどこ？ ここです
Wait, where are we? We're here
おかしいな いなー ハッピーバースデー！
Isn't it strange? Happy Birthday!
おめでとう！ え パーティーどこ行ったの？
Congratulations! Eh, where did the party go?
アキロゼのパーティーは？ ここがパーティー会場なのら
Where's Aki-Rose's party? This is the party venue nanora
さ え 何もないんだが
Now then... Eh, there's nothing here though
それでは アキちゃんに今回挑戦してもらうのは クロマキークイズです！
Now then, what we're going to have Aki-chan challenge is the Chromakey Quiz!
え、クロマキークイズって何？
Eh, what's a Chromakey Quiz?
え、アキちゃんご存じでない？
Eh, you don't know it, Aki-chan?
あー いいよ やったことないな
Ah, no, I haven't done it before
こちらはですね アキちゃんにこれを持ってもらいます
For this, we're going to have you hold this
そして 後ろの画面に映像画像が流れてきますので
And then, images and videos will be shown on the screen behind you
自分でクロマキーを動かして 何が問題の答えなのかを当てるというゲームです
so you'll move the chromakey to guess the answer to the question
えー 難しそう 大丈夫かな
Eh, it looks difficult. I wonder if I'll be okay
では早速クイズ行ってみるのらよ 行くのらよ
Well then, let's get right into the quiz nanora. Let's go
待って
Wait
第1問 仲間はずれはどれ？
Question 1: Which one is different?
仲間はずれはどれ？ 映像どうぞ
Which one is different? Here are the images
さあ誕生日パワーで見つけてくれ
Now, find it with your birthday power
みんなも一緒に考えて
Everyone, please think about it together
お、何なに。飲み物、これ。
Oh, what is it? Drinks, these.
もしかしてアキロゼが大好きな、あ、シュワシュワの。
Is it maybe Aki-Rose's favorite, ah, fizzy ones?
難しいぞ どれだ コーラ 難しいぞ
It's difficult. Which one is it? Cola. It's difficult
分かるかな ドデカミン
I wonder if you can tell. Dodecamin
あ、あ、あ！
Ah, ah, ah!
どした お、いたいたいた ちょっと嫌われてんじゃない？
What's wrong? Oh, there it is. Aren't you being a bit disliked?
あれ あれ 完璧に追ってみせる
Eh? Eh? I'll show you I can follow it perfectly
あー、あー！それ！
Ah, ah! That one!
当たった！見つけた！
I got it! I found it!
さ、答えをどうぞ
Now, your answer please
えへん これはアキロゼの大好物 ん、麦ジュース！
Ehem, this is Aki-Rose's favorite, um, Barley Juice!
正解！
Correct!
さすが 楽勝だ やったー！楽勝！
As expected. It was a breeze. Yay! A breeze!
簡単すぎたのらね 簡単すぎたな
It was too easy, wasn't it? It was too easy
じゃ、もう次はそんなに簡単じゃないから
Well, the next one won't be that easy
どんどん難易度上がっていきますからね
The difficulty level will keep going up
やめてくださいよ 分かった
Please stop that. Got it
それでは 第2問
Now then, Question 2
はい 余りの文字はどれ？
Yes. Which character is left over?
余りの文字はどれ？ そう、これですね 繋げたら一文字の単語になるんですけど
Which character is left over? Yes, when you connect them, it becomes a single word
いらないもの、余ってるものが3つあります さあ探してください
but there are three left over. Now, please find them
はい 動け動け 探せ
Yes. Move, move. Search
余るのが3つあるの？ そう
There are three left over? That's right
単語がいっぱい出てきてますね 何て書いてある？
A lot of words are appearing. What does it say?
むぎ こん です 姫 たん あ え
Mugi, kon, desu, Hime, tan, ah, eh
あん、あん、あん。あ。ち、ろ、え。
An, an, an. Ah. Chi, ro, eh.
ろぼ あ、ロボ むき たん
Robo. Ah, Robo. Muki. Tan
繋げたらどうなるの？ しす あ
What happens when you connect them? Shisu. Ah
あんぽんたん あ、あんぽんたんぽんたん
Anpontan. Ah, anpontan-pontan
ロボ ロボ あ、ロボ ひめ しす あ
Robo. Robo. Ah, Robo. Hime. Shisu, ah
余ってるかな これ
Is this left over?
分かったにゃ
I've got it-nya
さあさあさあ
Now, now, now
えっと まずじゃあ 繋がってた単語分かった
Um, well first, I figured out the target words
繋がってた単語はね あんぽんたんシスターズ！
The words were... Anpontan Sisters!
正解！
Correct!
あれ、待って 待って やった、正解
Wait, what? Wait. Yay, correct
あれ、やった正解 正解は何？あんぽんたんシスターズ
Oh, yay, correct. What's the answer? Anpontan Sisters
あ、あ、あ、シスターズ
Ah, ah, ah, Sisters
ま じゃあ一応ね
Well, just in case
まあ使われなかった単語3つ分かった？今のは聞かなかったことにしてあげてよ じゃあ あ、使われてないやつね 何があったかな
Well, did you figure out the three unused words? Let's pretend I didn't hear that. / Ah, the unused ones. What were they?
待って。一つ。
Wait. One thing.
あった。
There was.
姫！
Hime!
姫！おっ！
Hime! Oh!
ロボ！
Robo!
ロボ！おっ！
Robo! Oh!
ムキ！
Muki!
正解！
Correct!
なぜムキなんだよ！
Why is it "Muki"!
ムキ！
Muki!
そこはアキだろ！
It should be "Aki" there!
ムキでしょ！
It's "Muki", right!
It's "Muki"!
「まんことシスターズ」ってあったんだよ、本当は。
There were "Mankoto Sisters" actually.
あったねー。
There were.
そう。
Yeah.
あったんですよ。
There were.
見つけたわ。
Found it.
続きまして…
Moving on...
第3問行っちゃおうかな！
Let's go to question 3!
第3問は！
Question 3 is!
こちら！
This one!
問題 本物はどれ？
Question: Which one is the real one?
本物？本物？
Real one? Real one?
当ててみて頂戴！はい、どうぞ！
Try to guess! Here you go!
さあ、探すんだぞ！
Now, search for it!
おっ、ちょっと見覚えがあるぞ…
Oh, this looks a bit familiar...
何これ？いっぱーい。
What is this? So many.
何かがみんないるのに…
Everyone is here, but...
おっ！
Oh!
これは、ダック。
This is... duck.
シュバシュバシュバシュバダック。
Shuba-shuba-shuba-shuba duck.
本物はどれでしょうねー？
Which one is the real one?
アキちゃん探して！
Aki-chan, look for it!
アキちゃん本物って…
Aki-chan, the real one is...
どれが本物？！
Which one is real?!
行かないぞ！
Wait!
アキちゃん全部じゃないのー？
Aki-chan, aren't they all...?
ああー！時間切れ！
Ah! Time's up!
アキちゃんさ、どれ？
Aki-chan, which one?
どれにする？本物。
Which one will you pick? The real one.
え、本物はシュバルドダックしか見つからなかった…
Eh, I only found Subaru-duck for the real one...
時間ないからねー。
Not much time, right.
じゃあ、もう一回ちょっと見てみる？
Well, shall we look one more time?
本物のあれ、ちょっと見えてなかったからね。
The real one, I couldn't see it well.
サービスでもう一回挑戦！
A bonus challenge for you!
さあ、余すことなく探してください！どうぞ！
Now, search without missing anything! Go!
よし、よく見て！よく！
Okay, look closely! Closely!
この子本物じゃないの？
Isn't this one real?
端っこから端っこまでちゃんと！
Properly, from edge to edge!
ちゃんと見ててね！
Look carefully!
ちゃんと見てよーね！
Make sure to look carefully!
もう全部！隅から隅から隅まで！
All of them! Every single corner!
あっ！
Ah!
こいつだけ帽子が被ってない！
This one is the only one not wearing a hat!
正解！
Correct!
そこ？！
There?!
よく見て！何が違う？
Look closely! What's different?
本物はどれ？！
Which one is real?!
これはどっちを本物というべきなのか…
Which one should be called the real one...
見つけた！
Found it!
本物は…はい！
The real one is... here!
あれは本物のアヒルがいた！
A real duck was there!
正解！
Correct!
いたわ！よく分かったのらねー！
It was there! You noticed it well!
いや、シュバルドダックって言ってないからね、アキちゃん。
Well, Aki-chan didn't say it was Subaru-duck.
確かにね。
True.
先入観に囚われすぎないことも大事。
Important not to be too caught up in preconceptions.
そうなのらなー。
That's right.
さあ、じゃあ、最終問題！
Now then, final question!
第4問！
Question 4!
おっ！
Oh!
問題 間違っているのはどれ？
Question: Which one is wrong?
間違っているものは…
The one that is wrong...
さあ、探してください！
Now, please look for it!
これはちょっと自信があります、僕！
I'm quite confident in this one!
おけ！
Okay!
自信満々なのだぜ！
He's full of confidence!
行くぜ！さあ！
Here we go! Now!
あっ、文字が書いてある！あっ！
Ah, there's text written! Ah!
やっじまったピーナッツ！
Yatchimatta Peanuts!
2022年、最も使っていきたいワード第1位！
The #1 word we want to use most in 2022!
さあ、今回やっちまったか？！
Now, did we blow it this time?!
やったー！
Hooray!
やっじまってる、全部！やっじまってるな！
We blew it, all of them! We really did!
ちゃんと見て！何が見える？
Look carefully! What do you see?
何が違う？
What's different?
行かないよ、見つけてよ！
Don't let it go, find it!
さあ、見つかるか？
Now, will it be found?
さあ、どれだ？何が違う？
Now, which one is it? What's different?
ああー！時間切れ！
Ah! Time's up!
あー！分からない、もしかして！
Ah! Maybe you don't know!
分からない！
I don't know!
本当？
Really?
やっじまったピーナッツ？
Yatchimatta Peanuts?
えっ、何だったっけ？
Eh, what was it again?
ちょっと待って、えっ、何だって？
Wait a second, eh, what?
やばい、見つかってないかもしれない。
Oh no, it might not have been found.
え、ちなみにかっこう見えてたかもしれない。
Eh, by the way, I might have seen it quite well.
本当に映ってたのらよね！
It was definitely on screen!
結構みんな気付いたんじゃないかな？
I think a lot of people noticed, didn't they?
本当？
Really?
じゃあ、あと、もうちょっとだけね！
Then, just a little bit more!
お願いお願い！
Please please!
しょうがねーなー！
Can't be helped!
じゃあ、延長戦！
Then, extra time!
ゴー！
Go!
行くぜ！
Here we go!
さあ、もう映ってるかもしれないしね！
Now, it might already be on screen!
やっじまってる、全部やっじまってるんだよな！
We blew it, all of them are blown!
よく見てよく見て！
Look closely, look closely!
さあ、やっじまってるのか？
Now, did we blow it?
やっじまったな！
We blew it!
やっじまったピーナッツかにゃー？
Yatchimatta Peanuts?
やっじまってるよね、みんな。
We blew it, didn't we, everyone.
おっ！
Oh!
やっじまったピーナッツ！やっじまった…おっ！
Yatchimatta Peanuts! Yatchimatta... oh!
やっじまったポンナッツ！
Yatchimatta Ponnuts!
正解！
Correct!
当てたー！
I got it!
めっちゃポンしてるじゃんかよー！
You're totally "pon"-ing!
ポンしとるわ！
I'm totally "pon"-ing!
ほー、大正解！
Oh, perfect score!
いや、やっぱ最後に行くに連れて難しかったかにゃ？
Yeah, as expected, did it get harder towards the end?
いや、結構難しいし、ちょっと一言言っていい？
Yeah, it was quite hard, and can I say one thing?
いいよ。
Go ahead.
暑い。
It's hot.
めっちゃ！
Very!
ここで？！
Here?!
ここ、実はめっちゃ暑いんだよ！
It's actually really hot in here!
汗かいてるよ！
I'm sweating!
そうだよ！
That's right!
みんな涼しい顔してるじゃん、待って！
Everyone's looking so cool, wait!
ちょっと何かこれさ、不公平かなと思ったから！
I thought this might be a bit unfair!
そんな...
Well then...
アキロゼからも出しちゃおうかな、クイズ！
I'll give you a quiz from Akirose too!
え、本当？
Wait, really?
本当！二人にやっぱ汗かいてもらわないとさ、今ちょっと...
Really! I need to make you two work up a sweat, right now...
困っちゃうよ。
That's a problem.
動くとちょっと、トイレに行きたくなっちゃうから。
If I move too much, I'll need to go to the bathroom.
ダメだよ、それだけは逃さないで！
No, you can't run away from that!
ちゃんと探してもらわなきゃいけないからね。
You have to search properly, you know.
うわー！
Whoa!
やるの？
Are we doing this?
やるんだ！
We're doing it!
なんなの、白いの？
What's with this white thing?
知らないぞ、この流れ。
I don't know about this turn of events...
じゃあ、行きますか！
Well then, shall we go?
アキロゼからの問題は、こちら！
The question from Akirose is this!
問題 メッセージを読み解け！
Question: Decipher the message!
メッセージ？
A message?
これね、ルーナにいっぱい動いてほしいんだ。
For this one, I want Luna to move a lot.
頑張って見つけてよ。
Do your best to find it.
それでは、このメッセージはみんなわかるかな？
Now, can everyone figure out this message?
行くよ！用意、スタート！
Here we go! Ready, start!
え、何？何？
Wait, what? What is it?
待って、何が書いてあるの？
Wait, what does it say?
何？何が書いてあるの？
What? What's written there?
待って待って、え、これ？
Wait, wait, eh, this?
はい！はい！はい！OK！
Yes! Yes! Yes! OK!
明日も頑張れ！
Do your best tomorrow too!
ズズ、寝てる寝てる。
Zuzu, she's sleeping, she's sleeping.
出た文字を、頑張って文章にするんだ。
Try your best to turn the letters into a sentence.
え、ズズ？待って何？
Eh, Zuzu? Wait, what?
ユーケー、何何？
UK, what what?
ウルトラキング？アイあった？
Ultra King? Was there an 'I'?
アイ・ホ、アイ・ホ・ズズ。
I-HO, I-HO-ZZ.
あ、わかった人？わかった人いる？
Ah, anyone get it? Is there anyone who knows?
はい、もう一回！もう一回行ってみましょう！
Okay, one more time! Let's go one more time!
待ってちょっと、走るのが精一杯だよ！
Wait, just running is all I can do!
じゃあもう一回、頑張ってもらいましょう！
Then one more time, let's have you do your best!
用意、スタート！
Ready, start!
もっとゆっくり頑張って、早くね？
Try more slowly... wait, is it fast?
何の文字？ちょっと待って、マジで秘技使うわ、秘技。
What letters? Wait a sec, I'm seriously gonna use a secret technique.
秘技だ！ちょっと大きくする。
It's a secret technique! I'll make it a bit bigger.
なんか文字言って、文字言って！
Say some letters, say the letters!
GU... GIU... GIUSU...
アイ・ホ、アイ... アイ・ホ...
I-HO, I... I-HO...
アス、UK... ちょっと引いて、引いて！
AS, UK... zoom out a bit, zoom out!
もっと見つけて！ワード他にもあるの？
Find more! Are there other words?
アメリカ、GU... グッジョブ！
America, GU... Good job!
UK、US！
UK, US!
わかんねーよ！あれ？
I don't get it at all! Huh?
なんか文字になってきたような... グ... グッズ？
It feels like it's becoming words... Gu... Goods?
グッズ... 紹介... アキロゼグッズ？
Goods... Introduction... Akirose Goods?
はい、こちら！正解は、こちら！
Alright, here it is! The correct answer is this!
じゃーん！わかるでしょう？
Ta-da! You can tell, right?
見てもわかんねえよ！え、僕たち見てた文字だ、全部。
I still can't tell just by looking! Oh, those are all the letters we saw.
見たけどわかんない。ちゃんと読んで、ちゃんと読んで。
We saw them but didn't get it. Read it properly, read it properly.
ホグユケーアイ... クイズ下手くそか！
Hog-UK-AI... Are you bad at quizzes or what?!
US、アイ、アイ・ホ... アイ・ズ...
US, I, I-HO... I-S...
はい、ということで、グッズ紹介！
Yes, so the answer is, Goods Introduction!
ローマ字かよ！ふざけんなよ！
It was in Romaji?! Are you kidding me?!
弄ばれてるんだ、うちら。酷いよ！
We're being played with. That's terrible!
はい、ということで、グッズ紹介をさせていただきたいと思います！
Yes, so with that, I'd like to do the goods introduction!
おいおい、弄ばれたよ。あり得ない。酷いよ！
Hey now, we were played. Unbelievable. Terrible!
お祝いに来たのに、あの子に遊ばれちまったよ。
We came to celebrate, but we got played by her.
いい文章かと思ったのに！酷いよ！
I thought it would be a nice message! Terrible!
ごめんごめん、今日は誕生日ってことで、許してよ。
Sorry, sorry, it's my birthday today, so please forgive me.
仕方ないなあ... しょうがないならね、祝うか。
I guess we have no choice... Since we're here to celebrate.
じゃあちょっと、グッズ紹介一緒にやってくれる？
Then, can you help me with the goods introduction?
いいよ！しょうがないな。
Okay! We have no choice.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、ということで、グッズ紹介いきたいと思います！
Alright, so let's move on to the goods introduction!
なんだなんだ？
What is it, what is it?
ふふふ、こちらだ！どどん！
Hehehe, it's this! Ta-da!
ロゼ隊証明書＆ロゼ隊ピンバッジBOX
Rosetai Certificate & Rosetai Pin Badge BOX
一つ目！
Number one!
ロゼ隊証明書＆ロゼ隊ピンバッジBOX！
Rosetai Certificate & Rosetai Pin Badge BOX!
おおー！証明書とピンバッジ？
Ooh! A certificate and a pin badge?
これってもしかして、持ってたらロゼ隊の証明の証になっちゃうってこと？
Does this mean if you have it, it becomes proof that you're a Rosetai?
そういうこと！
Exactly!
欲しい欲しい！
I want it, I want it!
こちら、安住あきたけ先生書き下ろしの、豪華なボックスとカードになってるので、楽しみに待っててください！
This is a luxurious box and card set illustrated by Akitake Azumi-sensei, so please look forward to it!
楽しみー！
I'm looking forward to it!
二つ目、どどん！
Number two, ta-da!
ジョブズぬいぐるみとロゼ隊ぬいぐるみ！
Jobz Plushie and Rosetai Plushie!
おおー！ぬいぐるみ？え、これあったらもう寂しくねえな、夜。
Ooh! Plushies? If I have these, I won't be lonely at night anymore.
そういうこと！抱きしめようぜ、みんなで！
Exactly! Let's all cuddle them!
ぎゅぎゅっとな！
Give them a big squeeze!
そういうこと！え、こちら花田すみれ先生にデザインしてもらいました。
Exactly! These were designed by Sumire Hanada-sensei.
もうめっちゃ可愛くなって、なってるので、抱きしめて眠ってくれよ。
They've turned out so incredibly cute, so please sleep while cuddling them.
ぎゅぎゅっとな！
Give them a big squeeze!
見つめ！
Mizume!
ロゼ隊アイマスク！
Rosetai Eye Mask!
おお、すごい！
Whoa, amazing!
これ、アイマスクって、ぬいぐるみをギュッとして、
Wait, with this eye mask, if you hug the plushie
アイマスクしたら、もしかしてそれは、
and put on the eye mask, then maybe...
アキちゃんと一緒に寝てると思っちゃうってこと？
...you'll feel like you're sleeping with Aki-chan!
やべー！あらあら。
Oh my! My my.
夜のお供のワンセット、いかがですか？
How about this 'Nighttime Companion' set?
うわー！おいしー！ちょっと、寝れなくなっちゃうかも。
Whoa! Awesome! Wait, I might not be able to sleep!
大丈夫、大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
アイマスクが包み込んでくれるから。
Because the eye mask will wrap you up.
ああ、いいなぁ。
Ah, that's nice.
はい、さらにですね、今回ボイスもあります！
And what's more, there are voices this time too!
な、なんと！
No way!
すべてASMRにて録らせていただきました！
I recorded everything in ASMR!
ASMR、やばいやばい。もう寝れないって。
ASMR, oh man. You won't be able to sleep.
ちょっとこれタイトルも頑張って考えたから紹介していい？
I thought hard about the titles, can I introduce them?
何ですか？
What are they?
じゃん！「二人きりの誕生日アフターパーティー」。
Ta-da! 'Birthday After Party for Just the Two of Us'.
ちょっと待って、寝れなくなっちゃうって、こんなの。
Wait a minute, I won't be able to sleep like this.
やべ、ドキドキしちゃう！
Oh man, my heart's pounding!
そしてさらに、ヤンデレASMR！
And then, Yandere ASMR!
「愛され上手な君と、リンゴの皮剥き」。
'You, Who are Good at Being Loved, and Peeling an Apple.'
何それ、意味深。どういうこと？
What is that, so suggestive. What does it mean?
これね、台本を最初運営さんにあげたとき、
When I first showed the script to the staff,
ちょっとエッすぎて、やめてくださいって。
they said, 'This is a bit too much, please stop.'
そりゃそうだよね。
Well, that makes sense.
泣く泣くちょっと和らげたんですけど、
I reluctantly had to soften it a bit,
やっぱみんなヤンデレ好きだからね。
but everyone likes yandere, right?
みたい！聞きたい！
I want to see! I want to hear!
そして、褒めちぎりASMRリラックスバージョン！
And, Praise ASMR: Relax Version!
褒められたい！褒めて！
I've been praised! Praise me!
みんな褒められたい欲があると思って、今回叶えました！
I thought everyone has a desire to be praised, so I fulfilled it!
やったー！
Hooray!
ということで、こちらのフルセット、数量限定で
So, this full set comes in limited quantities
直筆サイン入りのポストカードが付いてるので、
with a handwritten signature postcard,
ぜひぜひぜひゲットしてください！
so please, please get it!
あるんですね。このフルセットには特典ボイスとして、
There's more. The full set includes a bonus voice:
さっきの褒めちぎりASMRの、
the 'Praise ASMR' from earlier,
「自己肯定感爆上げで気合入れたいときバージョン」も！
'Boosting Self-Esteem When You Want to Get Fired Up' version!
レベルアップしてるね！
It's leveled up!
これは特典にしか付いてないから。朝とかに聴いて、
This is only in the bonus. Listen to it in the morning and go,
「よし、今日絶対勝つぞ！」みたいなときに聴いてください。
'Alright, I'm definitely going to win today!'
やる気が漲ってくる！
My motivation is overflowing!
よし。ということで、行くよみんな！
Alright. Well then, let's go everyone!
お！ついてきて！
Oh! Follow me!
え？どこ行くの？
Eh? Where are we going?
せーの、シュシュシュシュシュ！
One, two, shu-shu-shu-shu-shu!
アキロゼのステージにみんなようこそ！
Welcome everyone to Aki-chan's stage!
すごーい！ロゼ隊おる、ロゼ隊おる。
Amazing! Rosetai are here, Rosetai are here.
みんなここでひっそり隠れてたんだね。
So everyone was quietly hiding here.
アリスの世界だ！
It's the world of Alice!
今日はここで一緒に踊ってくれる？いいよー！
Will you dance with me here today? Sure thing!
バッチリ衣装も着替えてきたね。
We've perfectly changed our outfits too.
いつも口車で任せばかり喋ってる
Always talking with just smooth words
Yes No どちらでもないこともあるでしょう
There are things that are neither Yes nor No, right?
いつだって世界は私を楽しくさせていて
The world is always making me have fun
いつか動けなくなる時まで遊んでね
Play with me until the time I can't move anymore
シャクシャク余裕を持って暮らしたい
I want to live with plenty of leisure
約束だって守りたい
I want to keep my promises too
誰かを愛することなんて本当はとても簡単だ
Loving someone is actually very simple
ずいぶんと遠くまで流され流されて切ないね
Washed away, washed away so far, it's painful, isn't it?
大切な思い出さえ忘れていきそうで
It feels like I'm going to forget even precious memories
確かに君に会いたい
I certainly want to see you
100年先もそばにいたい
I want to be by your side even a hundred years from now
どんなに離れ離れでも二人を繋ぐ呪文は JOY
No matter how far apart we are, the spell that connects us is JOY
樫の木が揺れる日は
On the day the oak tree sways
すぐに思い出してね 私
Remember me right away
いつもこっちからでも
Even though it's always from my end,
勝手ばかり喋っている
I'm always just talking selfishly.
運命は必然じゃなく
Fate isn't an inevitability,
偶然出来ている
it's made of coincidences.
いつまで経ってもわかんない
No matter how much time passes, I don't understand.
約束だって破りたい
I even want to break my promises.
誰かを愛す事なんて
To love someone is
唐突とっても困難だ
abruptly and extremely difficult.
たしかに君に会いたい
I certainly want to see you.
100年先も側にいたい
I want to be by your side 100 years from now.
どんなに離ればなれでも
No matter how far apart we are,
二人をつなぐ魔法は JOY!
the magic that connects us is JOY!
死ぬまでドキドキしたいわ
I want to feel my heart throb until I die.
死ぬまでワクワクしたいわ
I want to be excited until I die.
死ぬまでドキドキしたいわ
I want to feel my heart throb until I die.
死ぬまでワクワクしたいわ
I want to be excited until I die.
あ、この曲は！
Oh, this song is!
あ、準備しなきゃなのら！
Ah, I have to get ready nanora!
ほらほら行って行って！
Come on, go, go!
頑張って！
Good luck!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
待っててね！
Wait for me!
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
助けてね！
Help me out!
よし、じゃあ今からみんなのところに行くよ！
Alright, I'm heading over to everyone now!
君のヒロインはだーれ？
Who is your heroine?
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine Audition
覚えてる 優しい
I remember your kind
君の言葉にギュンとして
words and they make my heart tighten.
上手に言えない
Instead of saying it well,
代わりに笑いかけてみたの
I tried to smile at you.
目が合った気がした それだけで
I felt like our eyes met, and with just that,
鼓動が跳ねた お願い
my heart jumped. Please,
勘違いじゃありませんように
I hope it's not a misunderstanding.
そっとパノラマの中で 熱い視線送った
Quietly within the panorama, I sent a passionate gaze.
振り向いててね 目が合っちゃっていた
Keep looking back, our eyes have met.
ヒロインオーディション エントリーしたら
Heroine Audition. If I enter,
私を選んでくれるかな？
will you choose me?
マジ目だ せっかく
I'm serious. For once,
おはようだけで伝わるよ
just "good morning" gets the message across.
何気ない つぶやき
A casual tweet.
もしかしてドキドキ期待してる
Maybe I'm expecting my heart to throb.
眩しい 素敵な人ばかりで
There are only dazzling, wonderful people around,
自信もなくて それでも
and I have no confidence. But even so,
本音は
my true feelings are...
365日 もっと近づきたい
365 days, I want to get closer.
私なりのペースになるけど
It'll be at my own pace, though.
ヒロインオーディション 勇気を出したら
Heroine Audition. If I gather my courage,
君はねえ応えてくれるかな？
hey, will you answer me?
出会った一瞬ってかなりすごいミラクル
The moment we met was quite a great miracle.
このチャンスは赤い糸
This chance is the red thread of fate.
ギュッとたぐり寄せて運命にしよう
Let's pull it tight and make it destiny.
信じて真っ直ぐ背伸びの言葉に
Believing, straight towards words I've stretched myself to say.
...して
...hug me tight.
君のヒロインは私だよね？
I'm your heroine, right?
きっと君の心は
I'm sure that your heart
動かしてみせるよ
I'll manage to move it.
まだまだ全部足りないけど
It's still not enough at all, but...
ヒロインオーディション
Heroine Audition
選んでほしいの私を
I want you to choose me
いつかギュッとしてほしい
I want you to hug me tight someday
ありがとうずっと
Thank you, always
大好きだよ！
I love you!
ありがとう！バイバイ！
Thank you! Bye bye!
白い雪のプリンセスは
作詞・作曲：のぼる↑
The Snow White Princess Is
Lyrics & Composition: Noboru↑
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, mirror on the wall
世界で一番可愛いのは
Who is the fairest of them all?
やめてよ 棘のような視線刺さる
Stop it, those thorn-like gazes are piercing me
お呼び立てした彼女が
The girl who was summoned
素敵な晩餐もてなした
Served a wonderful dinner
そっと口に含んだ
Softly placed it in her mouth
微笑み薄れゆく
Her smile fades away
意識の中で
Within her consciousness
夢を見てる
She is dreaming
いつかのおとぎ話
A fairytale from long ago
時が止まる
Time stands still
お願いキスで目を覚ましてほしいの
Please wake me up with a kiss
白い柩から連れ出すように
As if taking me out of the white coffin
突き刺さる憎しみは
The hatred that pierces me
ドラマティックな事情を
Even if it colors
彩っても
A dramatic situation
君はまだ来ない
You still haven't come
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, mirror on the wall
ネクタイ任せにおはようさん
A morning greeting left to the tie
ズルから妬みを買われてしまった
I incurred jealousy because of my cheating
7つの小人はいるけど
There are seven dwarves, but
助ける素振り知らんぷり
They ignore me without even a gesture of help
そっと指をつかまれ
My finger was softly grabbed
微笑み一粒の
A smile, and even a single
涙さえも
Tear...
拭えなくて
...cannot be wiped away
呼吸もままならない
I can hardly even breathe
視界失せた
My vision has vanished
消えたわだから早く駆けてほしいの
It's gone, so I want you to run to me quickly
理由は聞かないで答えられない
Don't ask why, I can't answer
望まない憎まれは
The unwanted being hated
深い愛の事情を
Even if it tells a story
物語っても
Of a deep love situation
もうすぐいなくなるのかな
I wonder if I'll be gone soon
途切れてく命の音
The sound of life breaking off
毒林檎を食した少女のように
Like a girl who ate a poisoned apple
眠りにつく
I fall into a sleep
お願いキスで目を覚ましてほしいの
Please wake me up with a kiss
胸の中の声届きますか
Can the voice in my heart reach you?
階段を上ったら
If you climb the stairs
ドアを開けるだけで見つかるよ
You'll find it just by opening the door
お願いキスで目を覚ましてほしいの
Please wake me up with a kiss
白い柩から連れ出すように
As if taking me out of the white coffin
突き刺さる憎しみは
The hatred that pierces me
ドラマティックな事情を
Even if it colors
彩っても
A dramatic situation
君はまだ来ない
You still haven't come
消えてしまうその前に
Before it disappears completely
La la lai... 誰も知らない
La la lai... No one knows
名前のない今を駆けていくの
Running through this nameless present
あの三日月へと手を伸ばして
Reaching out toward that crescent moon
La la lai... 君を知りたい
La la lai... I want to know you
声にならない臆病な明日を
Through this voiceless, timid tomorrow
たとえ何度迎えようと思う
No matter how many times I try to greet it
薄空がパチんと切られたその時
At the moment the thin sky was snapped shut
世界が逸れだしたみたいだ
It feels like the world has started to drift away
目に映る景色が悲しく笑うなら
If the scenery in my eyes laughs sadly
恐れず瞼を閉じてごらん
Don't be afraid, just close your eyelids
さあ 皆さんこちらへどうぞ どちらへ踊る方へ
Come, everyone, this way please, toward the dance
さあ 踵打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心の躍る方へ
Come, stomp your heels, toward where your heart leaps
蜃気楼へ飛び乗って
Jump onto the mirage
逆さまな世界乗りこなして
Master this upside-down world
La la lai... 止まない愛を
La la lai... A spell for wanting
知りたいと願うお呪い
to know an unceasing love
時を超えた叫びよ届け
Let this cry transcend time and reach out
La la lai... 君を知りたい
La la lai... I want to know you
何一つ見逃さぬように
So that I don't miss a single thing
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one
残酷な運命が 抗えぬ宿命が
Cruel fortune, irresistible fate
考える間もなく押し寄せ急かして
Rushing in without time to think
前が見えなくたって君を信じてみたいの
Even if I can't see ahead, I want to believe in you
恐れずに一歩踏み出せたら
If only I could take a step without fear
さあ 皆さんこちらへどうぞ どちらへ踊る方へ
Come, everyone, this way please, toward the dance
さあ 踵打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心の躍る方へ
Come, stomp your heels, toward where your heart leaps
さあ 皆さんこちらへどうぞ どちらへ踊る方へ
Come, everyone, this way please, toward the dance
さあ 踵打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心の躍る方へ
Come, stomp your heels, toward where your heart leaps
空飛ぶ鯨に飛び乗って
Jump onto the flying whale
逆さまな世界踊り尽くせ
Dance through this upside-down world
La la lai... 誰も知らない
La la lai... No one knows
名前のない今を駆けていくの
Running through this nameless present
あの三日月へと手を伸ばして
Reaching out toward that crescent moon
La la lai... 君を知りたい
La la lai... I want to know you
声にならない臆病な明日を
Through this voiceless, timid tomorrow
たとえ何度迎えようと思う
No matter how many times I try to greet it
夢ならば覚めないで
If it's a dream, don't wake me up
現実なんて身も蓋もないから
Because reality is so blunt and bare
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one
幸か不幸か
For better or worse
彼女が選んだ
The path she chose
道は女王へ
Leads to the Queen
続く道
The road continues
女王陛下のおなりー！
Her Majesty the Queen arrives!
私が女王様さ
I am the Queen
何か文句はあるの
Do you have any complaints?
私が歌えば誰もが釘付け
When I sing, everyone is captivated
すべてを服従させろよ
Make everything submit to me
あなたが女王様
You are the Queen
そうさ私が女王
That's right, I am the Queen
美しい歌声
What a beautiful singing voice
当たり前じゃない
Of course it is
ホーケス・ポーカス！ さぁ始めましょう
Hocus Pocus! Now, let's begin
私のミュゼット！
My musette!
ピアノ！
Piano!
ウッドベース！
Wood bass!
ドラムス！
Drums!
ブラスセクション！
Brass section!
みんな言うことを聞き 私のために奏でなさい
Listen to what I say and play for me
すべて私のものよ 私は女王様なんだからさ！
Everything belongs to me, because I am the Queen!
これはみんなで奏でるミュージック
This is the music we all play together
へんてこでも
Even if it's strange
止まらなくたって
Even if it doesn't stop
あわてた時でも
Even when in a hurry
ハッピーを感じてるのさ
I'm feeling happy
十人十色だけど
Everyone is different
重なればハーモニーになる
But together we become a harmony
理由は単純さ
The reason is simple
だって We love music!
Because we love music!
お話をしよう
Let's talk
昔話より
More than old stories
もっともっと素敵な
Something even more wonderful
おとぎ話
A fairy tale
それはありふれた
That's a common
魔法のフィロソフィー
Magical philosophy
みんなのハートに隠れた
Hidden in everyone's hearts
ミュージック
Music
ジャン！
Ta-da!
Aki Rosenthal 4th Birthday Live / WONDER SHOWER MUSICAL
【CAST】 -Alice- アキ・ローゼンタール
[CAST] -Alice- Aki Rosenthal
-Busy Rabbit- 兎田ぺこら
-Busy Rabbit- Usada Pekora
-Happy Singer- 常闇トワ
-Happy Singer- Tokoyami Towa
-Crazy Tea Time- 大空スバル
-Crazy Tea Time- Oozora Subaru
-Invisible Cat- 天音かなた
-Invisible Cat- Amane Kanata
-Twins Sister- ロボ子さん
-Twins Sister- Robocosan
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
-Empress- 星街すいせい
-Empress- Hoshimachi Suisei
携わって下さった皆さん！本当にありがとうございました！！
To everyone involved! Thank you so much!!
改めてアキロゼ2022生誕祭、ありがとうございました！
Once again, thank you for Aki Rosenthal's 2022 Birthday Celebration!
今日は、アリスの世界を題材に、やらせていただきました。
Today, we performed with the theme of Alice's world.
早速ね、紹介したいと思います。
I'd like to introduce the cast right away.
Busy Rabbit役の、兎田ぺこらちゃん！ありがとう！
Usada Pekora-chan as Busy Rabbit! Thank you!
Happy Singer役の、常闇トワちゃん、ことトワ様！ありがとう！
Tokoyami Towa-chan, also known as Towa-sama, as Happy Singer! Thank you!
Crazy Tea Time、大空スバル、ことスバルちゃん！ありがとう！
Oozora Subaru, also known as Subaru-chan, as Crazy Tea Time! Thank you!
インビジブ、インビジ... インビジブルキャット役の...
Invisible bl... Invisible... as Invisible Cat...
インビジブルキャット役の、天音かなた、ことかなたん！ありがとう！
Amane Kanata, also known as Kanatan, as Invisible Cat! Thank you!
そして、ハートの女王様、Empress役の、星街すいせい、ことすいちゃん！
And, Hoshimachi Suisei, also known as Sui-chan, as the Queen of Hearts, Empress!
そして最後に、アリス役をやらせていただきました、アキロゼこと、アキ・ローゼンタールです。
And finally, I am Aki Rosenthal, also known as AkiRose, who played the role of Alice.
今日は、こんな素敵なプレゼントを運営さんにもね、頑張って作ってもらいました。
Today, the staff worked hard to create this wonderful present.
こうして最高なステージ、ライブができること、本当にみんなのおかげです。ありがとうございます。
Being able to have such an amazing stage and live show like this is truly thanks to everyone. Thank you so much.
今日はこの後、メンバー限定配信があるので、メンバーさんは忘れずに来てください。
After this, there will be a members-only stream, so members, please remember to come.
あとグッズも、もうゲットしたかな？これから、絶対行き...
Also, did you get the goods yet? From now on, definitely go...
…としてね！
...as well!
ということで、今年のほー、お、お誕生日…
And so, this year's b-b-birthday...
ちょっと待って。
Wait a second.
今年の、お誕生日は、本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for this year's birthday!
おつあーる！ばいばーい！
Otsuaru! Bye-bye!
アキロゼもみんなのところに行ってアフターパーティーするぞ！
Akirose is going to join everyone for the after-party too!
みんな大スキ～♡
I love you all so much~♡
WONDER SHOWER MUSICAL
Akirose 4th Birthday Live